[dramatic music playing]
Jon! And. uh...
Hi. Mom. Hi. Dad.
I'm Lara.
We... We have a daughter?
Lara...
And Jon. you're back!
[stutters] It's Jonathan.
And what do you mean I'm back?
I've never been here before
in my life.
You were here a month ago.
We saved your father. remember?
What are they
talking about. Lara.
I... don't know.
What?
He doesn't remember me.
So. when we
changed the future. uh...
We rewrote Jon's entire life.
[keyboard clacking]
You know. most people prepare
for a Pentagon inspection.
[winces. groans]
That's a rather... severe look.
even for you.
Care to catch me up
on your little science project?
It's on a need-to-know-basis.
and you don't need to know.
We're supposed to be partners.
Remember?
No. Wilson.
you work for me. remember?
[door opens]
Hello. Lex.
Uh. Director Waller. you're...
Yes. back in charge.
I guess you work for her now.
[theme music playing]
So we've already done this?
Just you. Lara wasn't here.
But we're so happy to meet you.
[chuckles awkwardly]
Wait. I didn't exist?
Not technically.
[chuckles nervously]
Was I. like. an accident.
-Uh...
-[Lois gasps]
Look. look. look.
If... if things
didn't work out last time...
-They did.
-You saved me.
Stop saying that!
That wasn't me.
It was you. A version of you.
And you coming
back made everything better.
Then why is my future worse?
Beautiful day out. eh?
The weather is pleasant.
[sighs] So.
where are we now. Kara?
-The sky. over Metropolis.
-[gasps]
[Kara] Headed to Smallville.
No. no. I-I mean.
where are we...
with each other.
Are you... Am... I... [screaming]
[sighs in relief] Hey. did I
say something wrong up there?
Jimmy Flamebirdbird.
what do you want?
Uh. I guess I-I-I'd wanna be
a better friend. Kara.
I see. A friend.
Is that all you want?
I-I just wanna be with you.
What do you want?
I want to trust you...
but I am afraid
you will leave me alone again.
Kara. I...
[laughing] Oh good. you're here.
[clears throat] Kara. Jimmy.
this is Lara and Jonathan.
From the future... [chuckles]
Again.
Jon. you're back.
He's not that Jon. He's... new.
Yes.
Do not provoke him.
Understood.
Welcome. new Jon.
It's... Jonathan.
Hey. we should get
back on mission.
'Cause that worked out so well
for the last guy.
Uh. what mission?
The mission
General Lane gave us.
Wow. Dad just can't
stop giving orders.
Well. whatever got you here.
I'm glad to have Superboy back.
Don't call me Superboy.
I'm Superman.
Uh. we already have a Superman.
[chuckles]
Do you?
[chuckles awkwardly] Heh.
Superman this. Superboy that.
Who wants a super slice
of Pa Kent's world famous...
I'm done with this.
Or there's snickerdoodles.
Jonathan.
I-I know all of this
must be strange for you.
But if you need to talk...
-I'm here to listen.
-[Jonathan chuckles]
You think we can just
have a heart to heart?
Maybe give me
a motivational speech.
promise me a better tomorrow?
Yo-You think. what.
we're just gonna play catch?
I learned to use my powers
on my own. okay?
I defended the Earth on my own.
Because you weren't there.
No one was there.
I'm not here for you
this time. Superman.
Stay out of my way.
Jonathan. wait!
-[wind blowing]
-[groans]
[dramatic music playing]
Ah. this again. No.
Stop!
[Lois] You should try that.
Pa Kent. whoo!
That man can bake. [chomps]
Hey. don't worry about Jon...
[chuckles]
and time loops. okay?
Just tell me why you
and your brother are here.
Our mission is confidential.
Of course it is.
But General Lane sent us back
in time to kill Lex Luthor.
[chokes. coughing] What?
You traveled back in time
to commit murder?
[sighs] We're here
to protect the future.
What kind of future
do you come from?
In our time Luthor commands
a personal army of mind
controlled Kryptonian clones.
The Eradicators.
There has to be another way
to stop him.
You don't have to kill Lex just
because my dad told you to.
Y-Your dad?
Yeah. General Lane.
-That's not who...
-Salt and pepper crewcut.
always giving orders.
No. You told us
to kill Lex Luthor.
You're General Lane.
[chokes]
As you can see. Lexcorp
is paving the way to a safer.
more secure Metropolis with...
Save it. Luthor.
[Wilson chuckles]
Wilson. you're still here.
My apologies. Mr. Luthor.
But why don't you show
Director Waller
your latest project?
Ah...
It's... still in its infancy.
not ready for review.
-But over here...
-I insist.
Very well.
Director Waller.
allow me to present...
Project Eradicator.
[Slade and Waller gasp]
Once complete. this weapon
will put humanity back on top
as the world's dominant species.
Created from Superman's
own living tissue.
Eradicator self-repairs.
self-evolves.
and will function under my
complete direct mental control.
Mental control?
The hardware is not finished.
but once it is.
the Luthor gray matter
I put in Eradicator's brain
will let me
control him with mine.
You put a piece of your brain
inside that thing?
That's all I need to see.
Shut it down. Luthor.
Wait. you don't understand.
The Eradicator
will revolutionize...
No. you don't understand.
I'm not just shutting down
Project Eradicator.
I'm shutting down all of
Lexcorp. effective immediately.
[suspenseful music
intensifies. stops]
[both sigh]
Welp. I'm a horrible parent.
Me too.
Poor Jonathan.
Jonathan?
I'm talking about Lara.
Ugh. you think you're doing
your best as a mother. but...
Well. at least you were there.
I somehow missed our kids'
lives two times in a row.
Maybe that's it.
Maybe I'm the problem.
I'm the reason Lara
turned out this way.
Wait. what's wrong with Lara?
Wait...
where is Lara?
[Lex] Director Waller.
I-I'm... I'm working
for the good of humankind here.
[Waller] Out of my way. Luthor.
You see this?
That's a prototype
time travel device.
Imagine what we could do
once it's complete.
Yo-You'll... You'll be able
to go back to the past
and stop your enemies
before they even strike.
I've made my decision. Luthor.
Listen.
I've seen what's out there.
Superman's not even
the worst of it.
There are... things waiting
in space that...
Superman put his life
on the line when we needed him.
I'll take space aliens
over you any day.
You've not only failed to live
up to Checkmate's expectations.
you don't even look
after your own.
You.
-[blasts]
-Ahhh!
And who is this young lady?
I'm here for Luthor.
No. stop. stop!
I'm... I'm... I'm... [panting]
I-I'm just a scientist.
[Lara] Just a scientist?
[scoffs] You're the end
of the world.
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps. grunts]
[groans]
[pants]
-[roaring]
-[bones cracking]
[Lara screaming]
Just like Lara
to rush headlong into things.
Always trying to be mommy's
perfect little soldier.
Sorry. kids.
Whole site's locked down.
No one gets past me...
Especially Kryptonians.
Where's Lara?
Lara?
Is that the super-powered
teenager who tried to kill Lex?
They took the fight underground.
-[Clark] Who's they?
-[Clark. Lois. and Jimmy gasp]
[all screaming]
[both screaming]
You okay. Smallville?
Yeah. the sewage broke my fall.
Oh. good.
[Clark] Is Lara down here?
She must be.
And the sooner we find her.
the sooner
we can get out of here.
[loud thud]
[Clark] Lara?
[both gasp]
For a second. I thought
there was a monster down here...
Shh! There is
a monster down here.
Kal-El? Lois?
Let's split up. We'll find them
faster that way.
That is unwise. Jonathan.
The lead in this facility
is disrupting the...
Whatever.
I don't need your permission.
[groans]
Kal-El. Lois Lane.
can you hear me?
-[Jonathan grunts]
-Jonathan?
[groans]
[glass breaking]
[roars]
[Clark and Lois] Help!
[soft roar]
[groans]
[roars]
[Jonathan] No. no. no. no. no!
[shrieks]
Jonathan!
Lara. wait.
[panting] Which way?
I-I-I think she went...
-[snarls]
-[both gasp]
[roaring]
Where's my brother?
[Lara grunting]
[Lois] Ahhh!
[both grunt]
[grunts]
[roars]
[Clark] Lara!
[Lara grunts]
What is that thing?
It's an Eradicator.
But... this one is different.
[whirring]
[Jonathan] Back off!
[grunts]
Lara. you're hurt. Get back!
Don't listen to her.
Get behind him.
Lara. listen to me.
[roars]
[dramatic music intensifies]
No!
[roaring]
[train honks]
Stay away from my family.
[roars]
[upbeat rock music playing]
[grunting]
[glass breaking]
[gasping]
Kids. wait!
Our children...
are so disrespectful.
Come on. this way.
Bring your monster
to heel. Luthor.
I-I... I can't stop it.
Don't you two share a brain?
What happened
to "direct mental control?"
[Lex] I already told you.
the system is incomplete.
It won't respond to my commands.
Eradicator's in control.
-[dramatic music playing]
-[roars]
[Supergirl grunts]
[grunts. screaming]
Lara!
[grunts]
Lara! Lara!
-[roars]
-[grunts]
I am your opponent. [grunts]
Ahhh!
[grunting]
[Jonathan]
He's evolving too fast for us.
We've... We've lost.
Just like that other Jonathan.
There's... There's nothing
we can do.
Ow!
You are not the only one
who has seen
a different world. Jonathan.
I have seen other futures.
We can still choose
a better tomorrow.
[growling]
[roars]
Stay here.
I'll show you.
[grunting]
She's alone with that thing.
Clark. you can't.
That's a job... for Superman.
-[Supergirl grunting]
-[roars]
[grunting]
[roars]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
[roaring]
[screaming]
[whirring]
No.
[screaming]
Kara! Kara.
Why?
You...
are my better tomorrow.
[wind blows]
Kara!
Jonathan!
[wind whooshes]
What?
Not again.
My family needs me.
They need me.
[Kryptonian voices whispering]
[wind whooshes]
Enough of this.
[growls]
[screams]
[roars]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunts]
[growls]
[Jonathan grunts]
[evil laughter]
You... lose.
[fading evil laughter]
[music stops]
Kara!
Kara. please!
I am... too late.
She's not.
She's not waking up.
[Lois] Jonathan...
Are you okay?
I couldn't stop it.
Eradicator is loose
in the time stream.
So. who am I arresting?
What?
We haven't been
properly introduced.
Amanda Waller. Pentagon.
Director Waller. the kids
were just following orders.
They were sent here
from the future
to stop Lex
from unleashing that monster.
Uh... I was defending myself
from an assassination.
The prototype was never meant
to be active at this stage.
It-It's her fault.
That... th-th-tha-that...
[groans]
Slade. you tell them.
You saw everything.
Y-You know what I was
trying to accomplish.
What we were trying to do.
I tried to tell you. Alex.
[Waller] Wilson...
book Lex Luthor.
We'll sort out our...
new guests later.
What are we gonna do. Clark?
Kara.
the kids.
the monster...
How are we gonna fix this?
I... I think I know
where my powers are.
I think I can get them back.
[gasps] You can
bring back Superman?
I think so. but I...
I'll have to leave.
For a little while.
Clark. no.
No. you can't leave me alone
with these kids.
I'll fail them.
We know I fail them.
You aren't the person
who sent them here. Lois.
They need the real you.
This you.
But I need you. Clark.
Our whole future
is getting ripped away.
First Jon and now...
I'm only going away
for a little while.
We can't save the kids.
We... We can't save
the future...
without Superman.
[Lois] Promise me. then.
Promise me. Clark.
that you'll come back.
[shrieks]
[grunting]
[Clark] I promise.
[suspenseful music playing]
[theme music playing]